Department of Computer Science Technical Reports 1985-1995: Finding Aid
Engineering Library
- Applied Computational Geometry: Towards Robust Solutions of Basic Problems, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-192-88; Dobkin, David P.; Silver, Deborah; 1 item
- Efficiency of the Network Simplex Algorithm for the Maximum Flow Problem, 1988 October; Report No.CS-TR-193-88; Goldberg, Andrew V.; Grigoriadis, Michael D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Probabilistic Analysis of a Closest Pair Algorithm, 1988 December; Report No.CS-TR-194-88; Golin, Mordecai; 1 item
- System M: A Transaction Processing System for Memory Resident Data, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-195-88; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- Maintenance of Geometric Extrema, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-196-88; Dobkin, David P.; Suri, Subhash; 1 item
- Profiling in the Presence of Optimzation and Garbage Collection, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-197-88; Appel, Andrew W.; Dubat, Bruce F.; MacQueen, David B.; 1 item
- Management of a Remote Backup Copy for Disaster Recovery, 1988; Report No.CS-TR_198-88; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Halim, Nagui; King, Richard P.; Polyzois, Christos; 1 item
- An Experimental Comparison of Initial Placement Vs. Process Migration for Load Balancing Strategies, 1988 December; Report No.CS-TR-199-88; Alonso, Rafael; Kyrimis, Kriton; 1 item
- Distributing Workload Among Independently Owned Processors, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-200-88; Alonso, Rafael; Cova, Louis; 1 item
- Querying a Network of Autonomous Databases, 1989 January; Report No.CS-TR-202-89; Alonso, Rafael; Simpson, Patricia; 1 item
- Clocked Adversaries for Hashing, 1989 February; Report No.CS-TR-203-89; Lipton, Richard J.; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; 1 item
- Communication Complexity: A Survey, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-204-89; Lovasz, Laszlo; 1 item
- An Optimal Algorithm for Intersecting Three-Dimensional Convex Polyhedra, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-205-89; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Indexing a Hypertext Database, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-206-89; Clifton, Chris; 1 item
- Scheduling Real-Time Transactions with Disk Resident Data, 1989 February; Report No.CS-TR-207-89; Abbott, Robert; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Shared Virtual Memory Accommodating Hetergeneity, 1989 February; Report No.CS-TR-210-89; Li, Kai; Stumm, Michael; Wortman, David; Zhou, Songnian; 1 item
- Fingerprinting Sets, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-212-89; Lipton, Richard J.; 1 item
- Recursively Enumerable Languages Have Finite State Interactive Proofs, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-213-89; Lipton, Richard J.; 1 item
- Face: Enhancing Distributed File Systems for Autonomous Computing Environments, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-214-89; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Cova, Louis; 1 item
- A Probabilistic Relational Data Model, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-215-89; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Porter, Daryl; 1 item
- Network Flow Algorithms, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-216-89; Goldberg, Andrew V.; Tardos, Eva; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- SHIVA: An Operating System Transforming a Hypercube into a Shared-Memory Machine, 1989; Report No. CS-TR-217-89; Li, Kai; Schaefer, Richard; 1 item
- Decreasing Channel Width Lower Bounds by Channel Lengthening, 1989 May; Report No.CS-TR-218-89; Heng, F.L.; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; Lin, William W; Pinter, Ron Y.; 1 item
- Telematics Research at Princeton-1988, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-219-89; Abbott, Robert; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Barber, Brad; Blaze, Matt; Clifton, Chris; Cova, Louis; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; Kyrimis, Kriton; Polyzois, Christos; Salem, Kenneth; Simpson, Patricia; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- A Runtime System, 1989 May; Report No.CS-TR-220-89; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Random Walk Techniques for Protocol Validation, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-221-89; Barbara, Daniel; Palacios, Jose L.; 1 item
- Faster Scaling Algorithms for General Graph Matching Problems, 1989 April; Report No.CS-TR-222-89; Gabow, Harold N.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Almost Optimum Parallel Speed-Ups of Algorithms for Bipartite Matching and Related Problems, 1989 January; Report No.CS-TR-223-89; Gabow, Harold N.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Princeton Systemfest Proceedings, 1989 February; Report No.CS-TR-224-89; Princeton University. Department of Computer Science.; 1 item
- A Spider User's Guide, 1989 August; Report No. CS-TR-225-89; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- SPIDERY WEB USER MANUAL The Spidery WEB System of Structured Documentation, 1989 August; Report No.CS-TR-226-89; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- Triangulating a Nonconvex Polytope, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-227-89; Chazelle, B.; Palios, Leonidas; 1 item
- Maintaining Bridge-Connected and Biconnected Components On-line, 1989 August; Report No.CS-TR-228-89; Tarjan, Robert E.; Westbrook, Jeffery; 1 item
- Some Graphs with Small Second Eigenvalue, 1989 October; Report No.CS-TR-230-89; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Detecting the Intersection of Convex Objects in the Plane, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-231-89; Dobkin, David P.; Souvaine, Diane L.; 1 item
- On the Second Eigenvalue of Hypergraphs, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-232-89; Friedman, Joel; Wigderson, Avi; 1 item
- Augmenting Availability in Distributed File Systems, 1989 October; Report No.CS-TR-234-89; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; 1 item
- Visibility with a Moving Point of View, 1989 November; Report No.CS-TR-235-89; Bern, Marshall; Dobkin, David P.; Eppstein, David; Grossman, Robert; 1 item
- Algorithms and Data Structures for Dynamic Graph Problems, 1989 October; Report No.CS-TR-229-89; Westbrook, Jeffery; 1 item
- Data Structures for Formal Verification of Circuit Designs, 1989; Report No.CS-TR-236-89; Friedman, Steven J.; 1 item
- On Bounded Round Mult-Prover Interactive Proof Systems, 1989 December; Report No.CS-TR-237-89; Cai, Jin-yi; Condon, Anne; Lipton, Richard J.; 1 item
- Playing Games of Incomplete Information, 1989 December; Report No.CS-TR-238-89; Cai, Jin-yi; Condon, Anne; Lipton, Richard J.; 1 item
- Real-Time, Concurrent Checkpoint for Parallel Programs, 1989 December; Report No.CS-TR-239-89; Li, Kai; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; Plank, James S.; 1 item
- How to Store a Triangular Matrix, 1989; Report No.CS-TR240-89; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; Lipton, Richard J.; Sandberg, Jonathan S.; 1 item
- A Dynamic File Caching Strategy that Preserves File Consistency, 1990 January; Report No.CS-TR-241-90; Alonso, Rafael; Kyrimis, Kriton; 1 item
- Simple Hardware for Fast Interprocessor Communication, 1990 January; Report No.CS-TR-242-90; Greenstreet, Mark R.; Li, Kai; 1 item
- Maintenance of a Minimum Spanning Forest in a Dynamic Planar Graph, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-243-90; Eppstein, David; Italiano, Giuseppe F.; Tamassia, Roberto; Tarjan, Robert E.; Westbrook, Jeffery; Yung, Moti; 1 item
- Automatic Analysis of One-Parameter Planar Ordinary Differential Equations by Intelligent Numeric Simulation, 1990 January; Report No.CS-TR-244-90; Sacks, Elisha; 1 item
- An Advisor for Flexible Working Sets, 1990 February; Report No.CS-TR-245-90; Alonso, Rafael; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- File System Design Using Large Memories, 1990 February; Report No.CS-TR-246-90; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Staelin, Carl; 1 item
- Coordinate Multi-Transaction Activities, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-247-90; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Gawlick, Dieter; Klein, Johannes; Kleissner, Karl; 1 item
- Two Epoch Algorithms for Disaster Recovery, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-248-90; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Hagman, Robert; Polyzois, Christos; 1 item
- Efficient Polygon Triangulation, 1990 February; Chazelle, Bernard.; 1 item
- Algorithmic Discrete Mathematics, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-251-90; Kenyon, Claire; Lovasz, Laszlo; 1 item
- Algorithms for Bichromatic Line Segment Problems and Polyhedral Terrains, 1990 March; Report No.CS-TR-252-90; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Guibas, Leo; Sharir, Micha; 1 item
- Debugging Standard ML Without Reverse Engineering, 1990 March; Report No.CS-TR-253; Appel, Andrew W.; Tolmach, Andrew P.; 1 item
- Design of the PRAM Network, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-254-90; Sandberg, Jonathan S.; 1 item
- Determining the Separation of Preprocessed Polyhedra- A Unified Approach, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-255-90; Dobkin, David P.; Kirkpatrick, David G.; 1 item
- Princeton Systems Fest II, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-256-90; Princeton University. Department of Computer Science.; 1 item
- Slimming Down By Adding: Selecting Heavily Covered Points, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-257-90; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Guibas, Leo; Hershberger, John; Seidel, Raimund; 1 item
- Competitive Paging as Cache Size Varies, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-258-90; Young, Neal; 1 item
- Concurrent Programming in ML, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-262-90; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- Some Complexity Questions Related to the Query, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-259-90; Ting, H.F.; 1 item
- On Evaluating Boolean Functions with Unreliable Tests, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-263-90; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; Kenyon, Claire; 1 item
- The Polynomial Hierarchy is Provable by Two Provers in One Round, 1989 December; Report No.CS-TR-260-90; Cai, Jin-yi; 1 item
- Generating Sparse Spanners for Weighted Graphs, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-261-90; Althofer, Ingo; Das, Gautam; Dobkin, David P.; Joseph, Deborah; 1 item
- Short Encodings of Evolving Structures, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-265-90; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Thurston, William P.; 1 item
- Concurrent Programming in ML, undated; Report No.CS-TR-262-90; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- On Evaluating Boolean Functions with Unreliable Tests, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-263-90; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; Kenyon, Claire; 1 item
- Unique Binary Search Tree Representations and Equality-Testing of Sets and Sequences, 1990 November; Report No.CS-TR-267-90; Sundar, Rajamani; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Triangulating a Simple Polygon in Linear Time, 1990 May; Report No.CS-TR-264-90; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- A Code Generation Interface for ANSI C, 1990 July; Report No.CS-TR-270-90; Fraser, Christopher; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- Short Encodings of Evolving Structures, 1990 April; Report No.CS-TR-265-90; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Thurston, William P.; 1 item
- More Efficient Bottom-Up Tree Pattern Matching, 1990 May; Report No.CS-TR-268-90; Cai, Jin-yi; Paige, Robert; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Testing Parallel Simulators for Two-Dimmensional Lattice-Gas Automata, 1990 June; Report No.CS-TR-269-90; Squier, Richard; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Unique Binary Search Tree Representations and Equality-Testing of Sets and Sequences, 1990 November; Report No.CS-TR-267-90; Sundar, Rajamani; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Comparison of Tree and Straight-Line Clocking for Long Systolic Arrays, 1990 June; Report No.CS-TR-271-90; Dikaiakos, Marios D.; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Data Sharing in a Large Heterogeneous Environment, 1990 July; Report No.CS-TR-272-90; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Cohn, Steve; 1 item
- Clover: A Timing Constraints Verification System, 1990 July; Report No.CS-TR-274-90; Doukas, Dimitris A.; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; 1 item
- Virtual Memory Primitives for User Programs, 1990 July; Report No.CS-TR-276-90; Appel, Andrew W.; Li, Kai; 1 item
- METEOR: A Constraint-Based FIR Filter Design Program, 1990 August; Report No.CS-TR-278-90; Kaiser, J.F.; Parks, T.W.; Steiglitz, K.; 1 item
- EIN Kleiner Filter Compiler, 1990 August; Report No.CS-TR-279-90; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Reconfigurability and Reliability of Stystolic/Wavefront Arrays, 1990 August; Report No.CS-TR-280-90; Sha, Edwin Hsing-Mean; 1 item
- A Rapid Hierarchical Radiosity Algorithm for Unoccluded Environments, 1990 August; Report No.CS-TR-281-90; Hanrahan, Pat; Salzman, David; 1 item
- Clustering Active Disk Data to Improve Disk Performance, 1990 September; Report No.CS-TR-283-90; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Staelin, Carl; 1 item
- The Spectra of Infinite Hypertrees, 1990 September; Report No.CS-TR-285-90; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Scheduling I/O Requests with Deadlines: A Performance Evaluation, 1990 October; Report No.CS-TR-287-90; Abbott, Robert; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Counting and Cutting Cycles of Lines and Rods in Space, 1990 October; Report No.CS-TR-288-90; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Guibas, Leo; Pollack, Richard; Seidel, Raimund; Sharir, Micha; Snoeyink, Jack; 1 item
- Verifications and Sensitivity Analysis of Minimum Spanning Trees in Linear Time, 1990 July; Report No.CS-TR-289-90; Rauch, Monika; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Quasi-Optimal Upper Bounds for Simplex Range Searching and New Zone Theorems, 1990 October; Report No.CS-TR-290-90; Chazelle, B.; Sharir, Micha; Welzl, Emo; 1 item
- Real-Time Concurrent Collection in User Mode, 1990 October; Report No.CS-TR-291-90; Li, Kai; 1 item
- A Note on Poset Geometries, 1990 October; Report No.CS-TR-292-90; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Lines in Space: Combinatorics and Algorithms, 1990 January; Report No.CS-TR-294-90; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Guibas, Leo; Sharir, Micha; 1 item
- A Free-Market Exchange for Information, 1990 December; Report No.CS-TR-298-90; Lipton, Richard J.; Sandberg, Jonathan S.; 1 item
- Distributed Processing ofFiltering QUeries in HyperFIle, 1990 November 14; Report No.CS-TR-295-90; Clifton, Chris; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Fully Persistent Lists with Catenation, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-299-90; Driscoll, James R.; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
  - Triangulating a Simple Polygon in Linear Time, 1990; Report No.CS-TR-264-90; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Computational Kinematics, 1990 December; Report No.CS-TR-300-90; Joskowicz, Leo; Sacks, Elisha; 1 item
- A Linear-Time Algorithm for Finding an Ambitus, 1991 January; Report No.CS-TR-301-91; Mishra, B.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- A Retargetable Compiler for ANSI C, 1991 February; Report No.CS-TR-303-91; Fraser, Christopher; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- Markov Analysis of Qualitative Dynamics, 1991 February; Report No.CS-TR-305-91; Doyle, John; 1 item
- Literate Programming on a Team Project, 1991 February; Report No.CS-TR-302-91; Marceau, Carla; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- String Processing Languages, 1991 February; Report No.CS-TR-306-91; Grisworld, Ralph E.; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- Evaluation of Memory System Extensions, 1991 March; Report No.CS-TR-307-91; Li, Kai; Petersen, Karin; 1 item
- A Note on Matrix Rigidity, 1990 June; Report No.CS-TR-308-91; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- An O(mlogn)-Time Algorithm for the Maximal Planar Subgraph Problem, 1991 March; Report No.CS-TR-309-91; Cai, Jiazhen; Han, Xiaofeg; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Dynamic Perfect Hashing: Upper and Lower Bounds, 1991 March; Report No.CS-TR-310-91; auf der Heide, Friedhelm Meyer; Dietzfelbinger, Martin; Kleissner, Karl; Mehlhorn, Kurt; Ronhert, Hans; 1 item
- Efficient Maximum Flow Algorithms, 1991 March; Report No.CS-TR-311-90; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Probabilistic Behavior of Shortest Paths Over Unbounded Regions, 1991 March; Report No.CS-TR-313-91; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- Prolegomena to Any Future Qualitative Physics, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-314-91; Doyle, John; Sacks, Elisha; 1 item
- Checkpointing Multicomputer Applications, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-315-91; Li, Kai; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; Plank, James S.; 1 item
- Reliable Reconfigurable Structures for Array Architectures, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-316-91; Sha, Edwin Hsing-Mean; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Lecture Notes on Evasiveness of Graph Properties, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-317-91; Lovasz, Laszlo; Young, Neal; 1 item
- Randomized Parallel Algorithms for Trapexoidal Diagrams, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-318-91; Clarkson, Kenneth; Cole, Richard; 1 item
- Empirical Studies of Competitive Spinning for Shared-Memory Multiprocessors, 1991 March; Report No.CS-TR-319-91; Karlin, Anna R.; Li, Kai; Manasse, Mark S.; Owicki, Susan; 1 item
- The Demarcation Protocol: A Technique for Maintaining Arithmetic Constraints in Distributed Database Systems, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-320-91; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Long-Term Caching Strategies for Very Large Distributed File Systems, 1991 April; Report No.CS-TR-321-91; Alonso, Rafael; Blaze, Matt; 1 item
- Garbage Collection Alternatives for Icon, 1991 May; Report No.CS-TR-324-91; Fernandez, Mary; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- Computations Over Infinite Groups, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-325-91; Cai, Jin-yi; 1 item
- Callee-save Registers in Continuation-passing Style, 1991 August; Report No.CS-TR-326-91; Appel, Andrew W.; Shao, Zhong; 1 item
- Polygon Triangulation in O(N LOG N) Time with Simple Data Structures, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-327-91; Kirkpatrick, David G.; Klawe, Maria M.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Probabilistic Diagnosis of Hot Spots, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-328-91; Barbara, Daniel; Lipton, Richard J.; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- Standard ML of New Jersey, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-329-91; Appel, Andrew W.; MacQueen, David B.; 1 item
- The Analysis of Heapsort, 1991 January; Report No.CS-TR-330-91; Schaffer, Russel; Sedgewick, Robert; 1 item
- The Analysis of Heapsort, 1991 January; Report No.CS-TR-330-91; Schaffer, Russel; Sedgewick, Robert; 1 item
- Point Location Among Hyperplanes and Unidirectional Ray-Shooting, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-333-91; Chazelle, B.; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Computing a Face in an Arrangement of LIne Segmetns and Related Problems, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-334-91; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Guibas, Leo; Sharir, Micha; Snoeyink, Jack; 1 item
- Cutting Hyperplanes for Divde-and-Conquer, 1991 June; REport No.CS-TR-335-91; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- An Optimal Convex Hull Algorithm for Points Sets in Any Fixed Dimension, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-336-91; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Human Language Comprehension is NP-Complete, 1991 June; Report No.CS-TR-337-91; Ristad, Eric Sven; 1 item
- Improved Algorithms for Bipartite Network Flow, 1991 May; Report No.CS-TR-338-91; Ahuja, Ravindra K.; Orlin, James B.; Stein, R.S.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Error Detection in Arrays Via Dependency Graphs, 1991 August; Report No.CS-TR-339-91; Sha, Edwin Hsing-Mean; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Some Geometric Aspects of Graphs and their Eigenfunctions, 1991 November; Report No.CS-TR-340-91; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- A Smart Interface for Numerical Software, 1991 August; Report No.CS-TR-341-91; Sacks, Elisha; 1 item
- A Theory for Deadlocks, 1991 August; Report No.CS-TR-344-91; Loke, W. Tim; Tay, Y.C.; 1 item
- Clover: A User Guide, 1991 August; Report No.CS-TR-345-91; Doukas, Dimitris A.; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; 1 item
- Computer Science 111, 1991 September; Report No.CS-TR-346-91; Blum, Jeff; Feit, Richard; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Literate Programming Tools need Not be Complex, 1991 October; Report No.CS-TR-351-91; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- Ray Shooting Polygons Using Geodesic Triangulations, 1991 September; Report No.CS-TR-350-91; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Gringi, Michelangelo; Guibas, Leo; Hershberger, John; Sharir, Micha; Snoeyink, Jack; 1 item
- Distributed EZ, 1991 September; Report No.CS-TR-349-91; Campos, Alvaro; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- Debuggable Concurrency Extensions for Standard ML, 1991 October; Report No.CS-TR-352-91; Appel, Andrew W.; Tolmach, Andrew P.; 1 item
- Dynamic Hierarchical Caching in Large-Scale Distributed File Systems, 1991 October; Report No.CS-TR-353-91; Alonso, Rafael; Blaze, Matt; 1 item
  - undated, 1 item
- Processing of Read-Only Queries at a Remote Backup, 1991 November; Report No.CS-TR-354-91; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Polyzois, Christos; 1 item
- NFS Tracing by Passive Network Monitoring, 1991 November; Report No.CS-TR-355-91; Blaze, Matt; 1 item
- Computing Minimal Spanning Subgraphs in Linear Time, 1991 December; Report No.CS-TR-356-91; Han, Xiaofeg; Kelsen, Pierre; Ramachandran, Vijaya; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- On the BIT Extraction Problem, 1991 December; Report No.CS-TR-357-91; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Derandomizing an Output-Sensitive Convex Hull Algorithm in Three Dimmensions, 1991 December; Report No.CS-TR-358-91; Chazelle, B.; Matousek, Jiri; 1 item
- Evaluation of Remote Backup Algorithms for Transaction Processing Systems, 1992 January; Report No.CS-TR-359-92; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Polyzois, Christos; 1 item
- An Empirical Comparison of Loop Scheduling Algorithms on a Shared Memory Multiprocessor, 1992 January; Report No.CS-TR-360-92; Blumrich, Matthias A.; Brownhill, Carrie J.; Li, Kai; Nicolau, Alexandru; 1 item
- Derandomizing an Output-Sensitive Convex Hull Algorithm in Three Dimensions, 1992 February; Report No.CS-TR-361-92; Chazelle, B.; Matousek, Jiri; 1 item
- A Monotonicity Theorem for Tandem Queues, 1992 February; Report No.CS-TR-362-92; Tay, Y.C.; 1 item
- Unrolling Recursions Saves Space, 1992 March; Report No.CS-TR-363-92; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- A Critique of Standard ML, 1992 February; Report No.CS-TR-364-92; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Nonlinear Heart Model Predicts the Range of Heart Rates for Electrical Alternans in Pericardial Effusion, 1992 February; Report No.CS-TR-365-92; Sacks, Elisha; Widman, Lawrence; 1 item
- Optimal Algorithms for Computing Connected Components of Bichromatic Line Segments and Polygons, 1992 March; Report No.CS-TR-366-92; Dobkin, David P.; Zhao, Jenny Zehong; 1 item
- Mechanism Simulation with Configuration Spaces and Simple Dynamics, 1992 March; Report No.CS-TR-367-92; Sacks, Elisha; 1 item
- Layout of Rooted Trees, 1992 February; Report No.CS-TR-369-92; Pach, Janos; Torocsik, Jeno; 1 item
- Software Support for Speculative Loads, 1992 May; Report No.CS-TR-372-92; Li, Kai; Rogers, Lawrene R.; 1 item
- A Comparative Evaluation of Cache Coherence Schemes Based on Virtual Memory Support, 1992 May; Report No.CS-TR-373-92; Li, Kai; Petersen, Karin; 1 item
- Supporting SPMD Execution for Dynamic Data Structures, 1992 June; Report No.CS-TR-374-92; Hendren, Laurie J.; Reppy, John H.; Rogers, Anne; 1 item
- Integration of Commit Protocols in Heterogeneous Databases, 1992 June; Report No.CS-TR-375-92; Alonso, Rafael; Ayellet, Tal; 1 item
- A Portable Multiprocessor Interface for Standard ML of New Jersey, 1992 June; Report No.CS-TR-376-92; Morrisett, J. Gregory; Tolmach, Andrew P.; 1 item
- New Jersey Line- Segment-Saw Massacre (Companion to the Video), 1992 June; Report No.CS-TR-379-92; Ayellet, Tal; Chazelle, B.; Dobkin, David P.; 1 item
- Data Structural Bootstrapping, Linear Path Compression, and Catenable Heap Ordered Double Ended Queues, 1992 July; Report No.CS-TR-381-92; Bushbaum, Adam L.; Sundar, Rajamani; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Depth Complexity in Object-Parallel Graphics Architectures, 1992 September; Report No.CS-TR-382-92; Cox, Michael; Hanrahan, Pat; 1 item
- Computational Geometry and Computer Graphics, 1992 August; Report No.CS-TR-383-92; Dobkin, David P.; 1 item
- Finding All Minimal Shapes in a Routing Channel, 1992 August; Report No.CS-TR-384-92; Chao, Liang-Fang; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; 1 item
- On the Fault Tolerance of Some Popular Bounded-Degree Networks, 1992 September; Report No.CS-TR-385-92; Leighton, Tom; Maggs, Bruce; Sitaraman, Ramesh; 1 item
- Engineering Efficient Code Generators using Tree Matching and Dynamic Programming, 1992 August; Report No.CS-TR-386-92; Fraser, Christopher; Hanson, David R.; Proebstig, Todd A.; 1 item
- Probabilistic Spaces of Boolean Functions of a Given Complexit: Generalities and Random k-SAT Coefficients, 1992 July; Report No.CS-TR-387-92; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Determining Single Connectivity in Directed Graphs, 1992 September; Report No.CS-TR-390-92; Bushbaum, Adam L.; Carlisle, Martin C.; 1 item
- Monte Carlo and Markov Chain Techniques for Network Reliability and Sampling, 1992 September; Report No.CS-TR-391-92; Bushbaum, Adam L.; Mihail, Milena; 1 item
- On linear-time deterministic algorithms for optimization problems in fixed dimension, 1992 October; Report No.CS-TR-393-92; Chazelle, B.; Matousek, Jiri; 1 item
- Smartest Recompilation, 1992 October; Report No.CS-TR-395-92; Appel, Andrew W.; Shao, Zhong; 1 item